<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourMania</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="category_shopping">Shoppings</string>
    <string name="category_museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="category_eating">Eating Out</string>
    <string name="category_tourist_places">Tourist Places</string>
    <string name="tv_dilli_haat_desc">Dilli Haat is a large market, which is quite similar to that of a weekly village market. The stalls are erected with thatched roof and the place gives a good blend of culture, handicrafts, music and much more. This is the best place to buy Indian handicrafts and artifacts. Dilli Haat opens at 11 in the morning and closes by 10 in the evening, even on Sundays.</string>
    <string name="tv_janpath_time">10:00AM to 9:00PM (Monday to Saturday)</string>
    <string name="tv_janpath_desc">This market is famous for paintings, leather articles, Indian artifacts, clothing, handicrafts, shoes, imitation jewelry, brassware and others. If you are choosing this destination, you ought to have good bargaining skills. You can find goods from many parts of the country and handicrafts of Tibet. This market is also called as the Tibetan market.</string>
    <string name="tv_janpath_loc">Janpath, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_janpath_place">Janpath Market</string>
    <string name="tv_dilli_haat_place">Dilli Haat</string>
    <string name="tv_dilli_haat_loc">Sri Aurobindo Marg, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_dilli_haat_time">11:00AM to 10:00PM (all days of the week)</string>
    <string name="khan_mkt_desc">This is one of the classiest street markets of the region. You can find a few branded outlets, some street vendors and other exciting shops. This market is famous for Ayurvedic medicines, government shops, books, cosmetic, clothing and others. This market is open from early in the morning until late night, except on Sundays.</string>
    <string name="tv_khan_mkt_time">10:00AM to 11:00PM (all days of the week)</string>
    <string name="tv_khan_mkt_loc">Humayun Road, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_khan_mkt_name">Khan Market</string>
    <string name="tv_chandni_time">All days of the week except Sunday</string>
    <string name="tv_chandni_desc">This is an ancient shopping region of Delhi, thriving until date. Enjoying this market region is like a small adventure tours. There are alleys and narrow passages, which lead to endless stream of shops. Starting from street food to fabric, you can find almost everything in the market. If you are planning to buy silver articles, the Dariba Kalan region of this market, is very famous. The market starts early in the morning and closes by late night. Chandni Chowk is not open on Sunday. This is considered as the best market for shopping in Delhi.</string>
    <string name="tv_chandni_loc">Chandni Chowk, Old Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_chandi_place">Chandni Chowk</string>
    <string name="tv_saroj_time">10:00AM to 9:00PM (all days of the week)</string>
    <string name="tv_saroj_desc">This is also a thriving market, famous for cheap articles. The articles of this market usually comprises of rejected goods from the packages sent for export. Due to surplus supply of articles, you can always find a better price with bargaining. Although rejected, the quality of the goods would be better than the ones used for local sales. Sarojini Nagar market is open on all days, except on Mondays. The crowd will be intolerable on Sundays. Thus, plan a weekday for your trip. Top things to buy here are designer clothes, fashion accessories, sweets and others.</string>
    <string name="tv_saroj_loc">Sarojini Nagar, Near Dilli Haat, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_saroj_name">Sarojini Market</string>
    <string name="tv_karol_time">10:00AM to 8:00PM (all days of the week)</string>
    <string name="tv_karol_desc">One of the oldest shopping areas is Karol Bagh. It is popularly known for offering an array of gorgeous bridal wears and traditional Indian garments. Besides, cosmetics, books, shoes, gadgets and electronic items are the things you can grab from the market places. There are some well known shopping places around Karol Bagh like Ajmal Khan Road (known for inexpensive readymade), Ghaffar (popular for imported good), Arya Samajh Road (visited for second hand books) and Bank Street (popular for gold jewelry).</string>
    <string name="tv_karol_loc">Karol Bagh, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_karol_name">Karol Bagh Market</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_mu_time">10 AM to 6 PM (Monday Closed)</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_mu_desc">Also, known as the National Museum of India, it is one of the largest museums in Delhi. Boasting of over 200,000 works of foreign and Indian art, this museum covers more than 5,000 years of worldwide rich cultural heritage.It is home to a plethora of departments such as archaeology, manuscripts, pre-history archaeology, paintings, arms and armour and much more.</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_m_loc">Janpath, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_mu_place">National Museum</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_hand_place">National Handicrafts and Handlooms Museum</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_hand_loc">Pragati Maidan, Bhairon Marg</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_hand_desc">Popularly known as the National Crafts Museum, MHHM is one of the largest crafts museums in Delhi NCR.Run by the Ministry of Textiles, Government of India, this museum is home to over 35, 000 distinctive pieces of craft; all of which reflect the amazing skills and craftsmanship of Indian craftsmen via embroidery, paintings, textiles and clay, wood and stone craft items.</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_hand_time">10 AM to 5 PM (Monday Closed)</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_rail_mu_name">National Rail Museum</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_rail_mu_loc">Chanakyapuri</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_rail_mu_desc">Focusing mainly on India’s rail heritage, the National Rail Museum has both outdoor and indoor exhibits with a toy train ride which allows visitors to cover the entire museum on regular days.Home to a fascinating collection of more than 100 real size exhibits of the Indian Railways, one can find displays of static and working models, historical photographs, antique furniture and signalling equipment in this best museum in Delhi.</string>
    <string name="tv_nat_rail_mu_time">9:30 AM to 5:30 PM (Monday Closed)</string>
    <string name="tv_doll_mu_time">10 AM to 5:30 PM (Monday Closed)</string>
    <string name="tv_doll_mu_desc">Being an immensely large collection of Dolls in the nation’s capital, this Museum in Delhi was set up by K. Shankar Pillai, a political cartoonist. Home to around 6,500 dolls from more than 80 countries, this is a popular Museum amongst children and adults alike.</string>
    <string name="tv_doll_mu_loc">Nehru House, 4 Bahadur Shah Zafar Marg</string>
    <string name="tv_doll_mu_name">Shankar’s International Dolls Museum</string>
    <string name="tv_nehru_mem_time">9 AM to 5:30 PM (Monday Closed)</string>
    <string name="tv_nehru_mem_desc">Established in the memory of Jawaharlal Nehru, this institution aims to preserve, recollect and reconstruct history during India’s struggle for independence.More than 2, 50, 000 printed books, 1, 50, 000 photographs and 8, 000 audio tapes reveal information on Nehru and the Indian freedom movement in this museum in Delhi NCR.</string>
    <string name="tv_nehru_mem_loc">Teen Murti Bhawan</string>
    <string name="tv_nehru_mem_place"><![CDATA[Nehru Memorial Museum & Library]]></string>
    <string name="tv_chacha_food_time">9:30 AM to 4:00 PM</string>
    <string name="tv_chacha_food_desc">Riding on high on reviews that can even put 5-star restaurants to shame, Chache di Hatti is one of the oldest joints in the heart of the north campus of Delhi University. They are known for serving the best chole bhature in Delhi University’s North Campus. Stuffed, melt-in-mouth bhaturas with optimally spiced chhole and special pickled salad is gonna make you go mmmm.  But one has to wait for a while here to be served, sometimes as long as an hour to get their own slice of heaven. Make sure to make a dash for this Delhi street food joint, for they sell out every day by noon!</string>
    <string name="tv_chacha_food_loc">32, Near All Smile Dental Clinic, Kamla Nagar, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_chacha_food_name">Chache Di Hatti</string>
    <string name="tv_juneja_name">Juneja’s, Amar Colony Market</string>
    <string name="tv_juneja_loc">74, Mehar Chand Market, Lodhi Colony, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_juneja_desc">A tiny little shop tucked away in the busy Amar Colony Market, you can easily spot Juneja’s by the swarm of people huddled in their chaat corner for an evening cup of tea and steaming snack staples of samosa, gol gappas and chaat. Juneja’s is known for having an enormous variety of sweets, which are actually worth dying for, especially their warq laden barfis. A must visit place for the ones who crave for yummy Indian sweets to satisfy their sweet tooth.</string>
    <string name="tv_juneja_time">12:00 PM to 4:00 PM, 6:30 PM to 11:00 PM</string>
    <string name="tv_paan_name">Prince Paan</string>
    <string name="tv_paan_loc">M-29, Greater Kailash (GK) 1, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_paan_desc">Stereotypes are not restricted to people but also to food. If you are a delhi street food enthusiast with an ironical knack for hygiene, look no further. Prince Paan serves an array of paan flavors like Butterscotch Paan, Strawberry Paan and even Paan ki Chaat! As for those obsessed with hygiene, they even serve Gol Gappe made in mineral water! Don’t miss their nimbu masala paan which is a raging hit among their regulars.</string>
    <string name="tv_paan_time">10:00 AM to 10:00 PM</string>
    <string name="tv_atul_desc">What was a run of the mill shop lost in the shoppers’ lanes of Rajouri Garden Market, is now a landmark for Delhi street food lovers. While the most popular treats are the aloo chaat and the tikki, it is the gol gappas and their sheer size that has every chaat lover raving about Atul Chaat. Since its inception eras back, this no frills outlet’s food is their one and only showstopper. Stop by at this popular delhi street food joint for a quick and affordable yet delectable bite.</string>
    <string name="tv_atul_time">11:00 AM – 10:00 PM</string>
    <string name="tv_atul_loc">H-44, Main Market, Rajouri Garden, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_atul_name">Atul Chaat</string>
    <string name="tv_kulfi_desc">Shopping in the buzzing marketplace of Karol Bagh is incomplete without the quintessential lunch at Roshan ki Kulfi. The specialty of the outlet is, no points for guessing, the kulfi-faluda, which is particularly a respite in the blistering and intolerable heat of Delhi. It’ serves one of the best kulfis in Delhi. Another Delhi staple of chhole bhature with a long tumbler of lassi is what has all the customers smacking their lips.</string>
    <string name="tv_kulfi_loc">2816, Ajmal Khan Road, Karol Bagh, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_kulfi_time">8:00 AM – 10:00 PM</string>
    <string name="tv_kulfi_name">Roshan ki Kulfi</string>
    <string name="tv_red_fort_time">9 a.m. to 6 p.m. and Closed on Mondays.</string>
    <string name="tv_red_fort_desc">Known to be one of the most popular monuments in Delhi, Red Fort has been standing strong as a legendary reminder of Mughal rulers. In the 16th Century, the walls of Red Fort were elongated few miles to save the city from attackers. The city was later taken by the British and the Sikhs. The tale of the former royal residence is shown every evening in Red Fort to take you back in the era of Mughal Dynasty.</string>
    <string name="tv_red_fort_loc">Opposite Chandni Chowk, Old Delhi.</string>
    <string name="tv_red_fort_name">Red Fort</string>
    <string name="tv_qutub_time">Sunrise to sunset.</string>
    <string name="tv_qutub_desc">Curve your neck to its most and there it stands with pride, Qutub Minar. It’s absolutely the best amongst the finest Delhi monuments. Known as an important heritage monument, Qutub Minar has its topmost point at a height of 72.5 meters. Crafted with beautiful red sandstone, this tower is famous for the imprints of Holy Quran verses. The complex but magnificent art of carvings on the walls has gained its names on the list of Delhi monuments.</string>
    <string name="tv_qutub_loc">Mehrauli, south New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_qutub_name">Qutub Minar</string>
    <string name="tv_india_gate_time">Always open.</string>
    <string name="tv_india_gate_desc">If Patriotism is engraved deep in you, then nothing could be as majestic as this historical monument of Delhi, India Gate. Built in 1931, India Gate reminds us of the victory and sacrifices made by the soldiers in the First World War. The arcade architecture has thousands of soldiers’ name inscribed on it who have sacrificed their lives. Another fascinating thing to see in India Gate is the Amar Jawan Jyoti under the arc of India gate, lit up all day and night as a tribute to brave soldiers.</string>
    <string name="tv_india_gate_loc">Rajpath, near Connaught Place, New Delhi.</string>
    <string name="tv_india_gate_name">India Gate</string>
    <string name="tv_humayun_time">Sunrise to sunset</string>
    <string name="tv_humayun_desc">This grandiose Delhi monument is actually inspired by one of the seven wonders of World, Taj Mahal. Built in 1570, Humayun’s Tomb is a burial chamber of the great Mughal King, Humayun. Set amid the beautiful garden, Humayun’s tomb was the beginning of changed Mughal architecture in India. With the overwhelming appreciation of this artistic monument, the Mughal rulers build such tombs all across the country.</string>
    <string name="tv_humayun_loc">Nizamuddin East, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_humayun_name">Humayou\'s Tomb</string>
    <string name="tv_jama_masjid_time">Sunrise to Sunset</string>
    <string name="tv_jama_masjid_desc">The Jama Masjid in Delhi is one of the biggest Mosques in India. The religious sentiments and the architectural splendor draw a lot of tourists to this place and made it a historical monument of Delhi. The Mosque is surrounded by three huge gates, four towers and two 40m high minarets constructed of strips of red stone and white marble.</string>
    <string name="tv_jama_masjid_loc">Opposite Chandni Chowk, Old Delhi</string>
    <string name="tv_jama_masjid_name">Jama Masjid</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
</resources>
